A Guide to the International Education Board records FA062
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Appropriations, 1920-1960; 1
  - Numerical, 1
    - Forestry, 1924-1927 (Box 14, Folder 209)
      Experimental stations, conferences, statistics, fellowships, research, reforestation, conservation. Asher Hobson, S. T. Dana, L. R. Jones, J. H. Oldham, John C. Merriam, Ray Lyman Wilbur.
      236.
    - Forestry, 1924-1927 (Box 14, Folder 210)
    - Forestry, 1924-1927 (Box 14, Folder 211)
    - Forestry, 1924-1927 (Box 14, Folder 212)
    - Forestry, 1924-1927 (Box 14, Folder 213)
    - Young Men's Christian Association, 1924 (Box 14, Folder 214)
      237.
    - Biological Journals, 1924 (Box 14, Folder 215)
      238.
    - Fisheries, 1923-July 1925 (Box 14, Folder 216)
      Stations, oceanography, conferences, A. G. Huntsman, John C. Merriam, T. Wayland Vaughn, Frank R. Lillie, Charles W. Eliot.
      239.
    - Fisheries, 1923-July 1925 (Box 14, Folder 217)
    - Fisheries, September 1925-1928 (Box 15, Folder 218)
    - Fisheries, September 1925-1928 (Box 15, Folder 219)
    - Johs Schmidt, 1925-1928 (Box 15, Folder 220)
      Expedition.
    - Commonwealth Fund, 1925-1927 (Box 15, Folder 221)
      240.
    - Farm Demonstration Work - Motion Picture Films, 1923-1927 (Box 15, Folder 222)
      "Better Homes", "What a Boy Can Do", "What a Girl Can Do", club work.
      241.
    - Farm Demonstration Work - Motion Picture Films, 1923-1927 (Box 15, Folder 223)
    - Farm Demonstration Work - Motion Picture Films, 1923-1927 (Box 15, Folder 224)
    - Farm Demonstration Work - Motion Picture Films, 1923-1927 (Box 15, Folder 225)
    - Farm Demonstration Work - Motion Picture Films, 1923-1927 (Box 15, Folder 226)
    - Farm Demonstration Work - Motion Picture Film Agreements, 1924-1925 (Box 15, Folder 227)
    - Farm Demonstration Work - Motion Picture Film Titles, 1924-1926 (Box 15, Folder 228)
    - Farm Demonstration Work - Motion Picture Film Titles, 1924-1926 (Box 15, Folder 229)
    - League of Nations, 1925-1927 (Box 15, Folder 230)
      242.
    - Veterinary Medicine, 1925-1934 (Box 15, Folder 231)
      243.
    - Conference of Agriculturalists, 1926 (Box 16, Folder 232)
      244.
    - Commissioner of Immigration, 1924-1929 (Box 16, Folder 233)
      245.
    - Atlanta University, 1933-1934 (Box 16, Folder 234)
      Negro education, endowment, buildings, equipment, Florence M. Read, Dean Sage.
      290.
    - New York State Colonization Society - Booker Washington Agricultural and Industrial Institute of Liberia, 1933-1938 (Box 16, Folder 235)
      Vocational and agricultural education, staff, construction, relationship to government, Jackson Davis trip, Thomas Jesse Jones, Jackson Davis, Charles T. Loram, J. H. Furbay, R. L. Embree, L. A. Roy.
    - New York State Colonization Society - Booker Washington Agricultural and Industrial Institute of Liberia, 1933-1938 (Box 16, Folder 236)
    - New York State Colonization Society - Booker Washington Agricultural and Industrial Institute of Liberia, 1933-1938 (Box 16, Folder 237)
    - New York State Colonization Society - Booker Washington Agricultural and Industrial Institute of Liberia, 1933-1938 (Box 16, Folder 238)
    - New York State Colonization Society - Booker Washington Agricultural and Industrial Institute of Liberia, 1933-1938 (Box 16, Folder 239)
    - New York State Colonization Society - Booker Washington Agricultural and Industrial Institute of Liberia, 1933-1938 (Box 16, Folder 240)
    - New York State Colonization Society - Booker Washington Agricultural and Industrial Institute of Liberia, 1933-1938 (Box 16, Folder 241)
    - New York State Colonization Society - Booker Washington Agricultural and Industrial Institute of Liberia, 1933-1938 (Box 16, Folder 242)
    - New York State Colonization Society - Booker Washington Agricultural and Industrial Institute of Liberia, 1939 (Box 17, Folder 243)
    - American Chemical Society, 1925-1928 (Box 17, Folder 244)
      Chemical Abstracts.
      291.
    - Scientific Publications - International Exchange, 1924-1925 (Box 17, Folder 245)
      304.
    - New Jersey - Rothamsted Experiment Station, 1924-1927 (Box 17, Folder 246)
      Exchange of soil scientists. Charles Skinner, Harold Sandon.
      305.
    - Princeton University - Oxford University, 1928 (Box 17, Folder 247)
      Exchange in mathematics, Oswald Veblen, G. H. Hardy.
    - University of Manchester - University of Michigan, 1926-1929 (Box 17, Folder 248)
      Exchange in physics - James M. Cork, J. M. Nuttall.
    - Latin American - Education Study, 1925-1926 (Box 17, Folder 249)
      Teachers College; secondary education. I. L. Kandel, James Doster.
      306.
    - League of Nations Library, 1924-1925 (Box 17, Folder 250)
      307.
    - Agricultural Economics Centers of Europe - Study, 1924-1927 (Box 17, Folder 251)
      With the International Institute of Agriculture. Asher Hobson.
      308.
    - Cornell University - University of Leeds, 1925-1930 (Box 17, Folder 252)
      Exchange in plant physiology. Otis Curtis, William Pearsall.
      309.
    - Library Training, 1924-1925 (Box 17, Folder 253)
      310.
    - Library Fellowships, 1926 (Box 17, Folder 254)
      310.1
    - Scientific Literature, 1926-1927 (Box 17, Folder 255)
      Purchase of literature and equipment.
      312.
    - Marine Biological Stations - Europe, 1927 (Box 17, Folder 256)
      313.
    - Maine Agricultural Extension Service, 1923 (Box 17, Folder 257)
      1001.
    - Vassar College, 1923 (Box 17, Folder 258)
      1002.
    - New York University, 1923 (Box 17, Folder 259)
      1003.
    - University of the State of New York, 1923-1926 (Box 17, Folder 260)
      1004.
    - George Peabody College for Teachers, 1923-1924 (Box 17, Folder 261)
      1005.
    - Harvard University, 1923-1934 (Box 18, Folder 262)
      1007.
    - Harvard College Observatory - Southern Station, 1925-1935, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 263)
      South Africa, endowment. Harlow Shapley.
      1007.1
    - American Association of Variable Star Observers, 1926-1927 (Box 18, Folder 264)
      Association with Harvard College Observatory. George E. Hale, Harlow Shapley, Frank Schlesinger, Harry N. Russell.
      1007.2
    - Astronomy, 1926-1927 (Box 18, Folder 265)
      At Harvard, classified fields of study and research.
      1007.3
    - Harvard University - Biological Institute, 1925-1931 (Box 18, Folder 266)
      Building and endowment. A. Laurence Lowell.
      1007.4
    - Harvard University - Biological Institute, 1925-1931 (Box 18, Folder 267)
    - University of Chicago Medical School, 1923 (Box 18, Folder 268)
      1008.
    - University of Chicago - Oriental Institute, 1928-1938 (Box 18, Folder 269)
      Expeditions and funds. Endowment, buildings, equipment, publications. John A. Wilson, Charles Breasted, Robert M. Hutchins, James H. Breasted, Frederic Woodward.
      1008.1
    - University of Chicago - Oriental Institute, 1928-1938 (Box 18, Folder 270)
    - University of Chicago - Oriental Institute, 1928-1938 (Box 18, Folder 271)
    - University of Chicago - Oriental Institute, 1928-1938 (Box 18, Folder 272)
    - University of Chicago - Oriental Institute, 1928-1938 (Box 18, Folder 273)
    - University of Chicago - Oriental Institute, 1928-1938 (Box 18, Folder 274)
    - International Institute of Teachers College, 1923-1933, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 275)
      Guidance and instruction of foreign students at Teachers College, supervise studies of American students in foreign countries, channel of information and exchange of educational contracts. Paul Monroe, James E. Russell.
      1010.
    - International Institute of Teachers College, 1923-1933, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 276)
    - International Institute of Teachers College, 1923-1933, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 277)
    - International Institute of Teachers College, 1923-1933, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 278)
    - International Institute of Teachers College, 1923-1933, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 279)
    - International Institute of Teachers College, 1923-1933, 1958 (Box 19, Folder 280)
    - Constantinople Woman's College, 1923-1924 (Box 19, Folder 281)
      1011.
    - Near East College, 1923-1927 (Box 19, Folder 282)
      1012.
    - International College - Turkey, 1923-1925 (Box 19, Folder 283)
      1013.
    - Foreign Agriculture Experiment Stations, 1923-1928 (Box 19, Folder 284)
      1014.
    - New York State College of Agriculture, 1923-1936 (Box 19, Folder 285)
      Biometrics, plant breeding and genetics at Cornell. H. H. Love, Livingston Farrand.
      1015.
    - New York State College of Agriculture, 1923-1936 (Box 19, Folder 286)
    - New York State College of Agriculture, 1923-1936 (Box 19, Folder 287)
    - New York State College of Agriculture, 1923-1936 (Box 19, Folder 288)
    - Thompson Institute for Plant Research, 1923-1926 (Box 20, Folder 289)
      1016.
    - Polytechnic Institute of Puerto Rico, 1923-1924 (Box 20, Folder 290)
      1017.
    - Massachusetts Agricultural Colleges, 1924 (Box 20, Folder 291)
      1018.
    - International Institute of Agriculture - Rome, 1923-1933 (Box 20, Folder 292)
      World agriculture census, library, forestry congress, student training. President DeMichaelis, Asher Hobson, Carol Dragoni.
      1019.
    - International Institute of Agriculture - Rome, 1923-1933 (Box 20, Folder 293)
    - International Institute of Agriculture - Rome, 1923-1933 (Box 20, Folder 294)
    - International Institute of Agriculture - Rome, 1923-1933 (Box 20, Folder 295)
    - International Institute of Agriculture - Rome, 1923-1933 (Box 20, Folder 296)
    - International Institute of Agriculture - Rome, 1923-1933 (Box 20, Folder 297)
    - International Institute of Agriculture - Rome, 1923-1933 (Box 20, Folder 298)
    - University of Wisconsin - College of Agriculture, 1924-1926 (Box 20, Folder 299)
      1020.
    - A. W. Ashby, 1923-1928 (Box 20, Folder 300)
      1021.
    - Pennsylvania State College, 1924-1925 (Box 20, Folder 301)
      1022.
    - Michigan Agricultural College, 1925 (Box 20, Folder 302)
      1023.
    - Institute of Land Economics, 1925 (Box 20, Folder 303)
      1024.
    - Institute of Biological Research, 1925-1926 (Box 20, Folder 304)
      1025.
    - University of Michigan, 1926-1927 (Box 20, Folder 305)
      1025a
    - University of Minnesota, 1926-1928 (Box 21, Folder 306)
      1026.
    - Geology, 1926-1928 (Box 21, Folder 307)
      Pleistocene, paleobiology. David White, Vernon Kellog.
      1027.
    - Coastal Laboratory, 1926 (Box 21, Folder 308)
      1028.
    - New Jersey State College of Agriculture, 1926 (Box 21, Folder 309)
      1029.
    - European Herbaria, 1926-1927 (Box 21, Folder 310)
      Natural history museums. David Fairchild, A. Wetmore.
      1030.
    - University of Virginia, 1927-1935 (Box 21, Folder 311)
      1031.
    - California Institute of Technology - Observatory, 1926-1931 (Box 21, Folder 312)
      Palomar; work on drawings, blueprints - disks, mirrors, Corning Glass, pyrex, Thompson Research Laboratory, George E. Hale, Arthur L. Day, Amoden Gage, J. L. Hostetter, Walter S. Adams, Robert R. Milliken.
      1032.
    - California Institute of Technology - Observatory, 1926-1931 (Box 21, Folder 313)
    - California Institute of Technology - Observatory, 1926-1931 (Box 21, Folder 314)
    - California Institute of Technology - Observatory, 1926-1931 (Box 21, Folder 315)
    - California Institute of Technology - Observatory, 1926-1931 (Box 21, Folder 316)
    - California Institute of Technology - Observatory, 1926-1931 (Box 21, Folder 317)
    - California Institute of Technology - Observatory, 1926-1931 (Box 21, Folder 318)
    - California Institute of Technology - Observatory, 1932-1933 (Box 22, Folder 319)
    - California Institute of Technology - Observatory, 1932-1933 (Box 22, Folder 320)
    - California Institute of Technology - Observatory, 1932-1933 (Box 22, Folder 321)
    - California Institute of Technology - Observatory, 1932-1933 (Box 22, Folder 322)
    - Agricultural Education in the United States, 1923-1927 (Box 22, Folder 323)
      Survey, preliminary contacts, general information, conferences. E. D. Ball, Chris L. Christiansen.
      2000.
    - Agricultural Education in the United States, 1923-1927 (Box 22, Folder 324)
    - Agricultural Education in the United States, 1923-1927 (Box 22, Folder 325)
    - Agricultural Education in the United States, 1923-1927 (Box 22, Folder 326)
    - Survey of Far East - Harry Luman Russell, 1925-1928 (Box 22, Folder 327)
      Includes material related to Harry Luman Russell's trip through Asia and survey of the scientific and agricultural education needs in Japan, China, the Philippines, Siam, Java, Australia, and New Zealand. Includes "Synopsis of Course of Procedure to Follow in Education Survey of Far East" by Russell.
      2500.
      Biographical / Historical
      Harry Luman Russell (1866-1954) was an American bacteriologist and educator. Russell was graduated from the University of Wisconsin in 1884, received an M.S. from Wisconsin in 1890, and a Ph.D. from Johns Hopkins in 1892. Russell then became a Professor at the University of Wisconsin. In 1903 Russell was made Director of the Wisconsin State Hygienic Laboratory, and became Dean of the University of Wisconsin's College of Agriculture in 1907. Russell was also a charter member of the American Society for Microbiology, and was named President in 1908. In 1925 Russell was commissioned by the International Education Board (IEB) to travel through Asia, and survey the scientific and agricultural education needs in Japan, China, the Philippines, Siam, Java, Australia, and New Zealand.
    - Survey of Far East - Harry Luman Russell, 1925-1928 (Box 22, Folder 328)
      Includes material related to Harry Luman Russell's trip through Asia and survey of the scientific and agricultural education needs in Japan, China, the Philippines, Siam, Java, Australia, and New Zealand.
    - Albert R. Mann, 1924-1931 (Box 23, Folder 329)
      Includes speeches, trips, projects, general policy, and administrative material related to Albert R. Mann's term as Director of Agricultural Education for Europe, and the IEB's program of agricultural education and rehabilitation in Europe.
      3000.
    - Albert R. Mann, 1924-1931 (Box 23, Folder 330)
    - Albert R. Mann, 1924-1931 (Box 23, Folder 331)
    - Albert R. Mann, 1924-1931 (Box 23, Folder 332)
    - C. B. Hutchison, 1924-1929 (Box 23, Folder 333)
      Includes material on projects, fellowships, conferences, policy, and administration related to Claude B. Hutchison's term as assistant to Albert R. Mann (Director of Agricultural Education for Europe), then Hutchison's term as Director, and the IEB's program of agricultural education and rehabilitation in Europe.
      3001.
    - C. B. Hutchison, 1924-1929 (Box 23, Folder 334)
    - C. B. Hutchison, 1924-1929 (Box 23, Folder 335)
    - C. B. Hutchison - Logs, 1925-1928 (Box 23, Folder 336)
      Scope and Contents
      Includes material related to C.B. Hutchison's term as Director of Agricultural Education for Europe, and the IEB's program of agricultural education and rehabilitation in Europe: "Yugoslavia, Agricultural Studies - Section A, Supplementing Log Section IX, C.B. Hutchison, Director of Agricultural Education for Europe, December 8-10, 1925"; and "Log Section 35: Switzerland (First Report), Summary of Interviews Inspections, and Other Activities, Part 1: Albert R. Mann, July 1-2, 1926, Part 2: C.B. Hutchison, December 19-23, 1927, January 18-19, 1928".
    - C. B. Hutchison - Logs, 1925-1928 (Box 23, Folder 337)
      Includes material related to C.B. Hutchison's term as Director of Agricultural Education for Europe, and the IEB's program of agricultural education and rehabilitation in Europe: Includes "C.B. Hutchison, Logs, 1927"; "Holland, Agricultural Studies - Section A (Supplementing Log Section 21), C.B. Hutchison, November 29-December 1, 1927"; and "Denmark, Agricultural Studies - Section A (Supplementing Log Section 20), C.B. Hutchison, December 3-5, 1927".
    - F. W. Atterbury, 1925-1927 (Box 24, Folder 338)
      3002.
    - European Agricultural Education Report, 1927-1928 (Box 24, Folder 339)
      3003.
    - Augustus Trowbridge, 1924-1931 (Box 24, Folder 340)
      French degrees, policy, projects, administration, reorganization, fellowships.
      4000.
    - Augustus Trowbridge, 1924-1931 (Box 24, Folder 341)
    - Augustus Trowbridge, 1924-1931 (Box 24, Folder 342)
    - Augustus Trowbridge, 1924-1931 (Box 24, Folder 343)
    - Augustus Trowbridge, 1924-1931 (Box 24, Folder 344)
    - Augustus Trowbridge, 1924-1931 (Box 24, Folder 345)
    - Augustus Trowbridge, 1924-1931 (Box 24, Folder 346)
    - Augustus Trowbridge, 1924-1931 (Box 24, Folder 347)
    - Augustus Trowbridge, 1924-1931 (Box 24, Folder 348)
    - W. E. Tisdale, 1925-1931 (Box 24, Folder 349)
      4001.
    - E. W. Lindstrom, 1926-1928 (Box 25, Folder 350)
      Genetics, fellowships.
      4002.
    - William J. Robbins, 1928 (Box 25, Folder 351)
      4003.
  - Foreign Countries, 2
    Projects and general information are filed under a given country. There is quite a lot of information about fellowships and traveling professorships in this subseries.
    This subseries is arranged alphabetically.
    - Africa 0 - General, 1927 (Box 25, Folder 352)
    - Albania 0 - General, 1927 (Box 25, Folder 353)
    - Albania 1 - Elmer E. Jones Report (Box 25, Folder 354)
    - Australia 0 - General, 1926-1931 (Box 25, Folder 355)
    - Australia 1 - University of Adelaide - Waite Agricultural Institute, 1926 (Box 25, Folder 356)
    - Austria 0 - General, 1924-1928 (Box 25, Folder 357)
    - Austria 0 - General, 1924-1928 (Box 25, Folder 358)
    - Austria 2 - Agriculture, 1925 (Box 25, Folder 359)
    - Austria 3 - Radium Institute of Vienna, 1923-1930 (Box 25, Folder 360)
      Maintenance, fellowships, literature, equipment. Stefan Meyer.
    - Austria 4 - Scientific Literature and Equipment, 1924-1931 (Box 25, Folder 361)
      Hochschule fur Bodenkulture, Royal Hungarian Veterinary College, Veterinary College of Vienna, Radium Institute of Vienna.
    - Austria 4 - Scientific Literature and Equipment, 1924-1931 (Box 25, Folder 362)
    - Austria 4 - Scientific Literature and Equipment, 1924-1931 (Box 25, Folder 363)
    - Austria 5 - Paleobiological Institute, 1926-1927 (Box 25, Folder 364)
      Equipment.
    - Belgium 0 - General, 1925-1928 (Box 25, Folder 365)
    - Belgium 1 - University of Ghent, Institute of Physics, 1926 (Box 25, Folder 366)
    - Belgium 2 - Foundation Universitaire, 1927-1934 (Box 26, Folder 367)
      Scientific literature.
    - Belgium 2 - Foundation Universitaire, 1927-1934 (Box 26, Folder 368)
    - Bulgaria 0 - General, 1923-1929 (Box 26, Folder 369)
    - Bulgaria 2 - Russian School, 1924 (Box 26, Folder 370)
    - Bulgaria 3 - University of Sofia, Proposed Biological Institute, 1924-1932 (Box 26, Folder 371)
      Cell stimulation, fellowships, cerials.
    - Bulgaria 4 - University of Sofia, Institute of Plant Pathology, 1925-1926 (Box 26, Folder 372)
    - Bulgaria 5 - University of Sofia, School of Agriculture, 1926-1930 (Box 26, Folder 373)
    - Bulgaria 6 - University of Sofia, School of Agriculture, 1926-1939 (Box 26, Folder 374)
      Buildings, greenhouse, equipment. Jan Molloff.
    - Canada 0 - General, 1923-1928 (Box 26, Folder 375)
    - Canada 1 - Ontario, Ministry of Agriculture, 1923 (Box 26, Folder 376)
    - Canada 3 - Ontario Agricultural College, 1923 (Box 26, Folder 377)
    - Canada 4 - McMaster University, 1923-1924 (Box 26, Folder 378)
    - Canada 5 - Canadian Study of Institutions, 1926 (Box 26, Folder 379)
      National Research Council (NRC) fellowships.
    - Canada 6 - Study of Canadian Institutions, Department of Science, 1926-1927 (Box 26, Folder 380)
      Thorkelson trip.
    - Canada 7 - University of Toronto, 1923-1928 (Box 26, Folder 381)
    - Canada 8 - University of Canada, Graduate Courses in Agriculture, 1926-1930 (Box 26, Folder 382)
      Survey, Canadian Society of Technical Agriculturalists. Robert Newton.
    - Canada 8 - Canadian Universities, Graduate Courses in Agriculture - Reports (Box 26, Folder 383)
    - China 0 - General, 1924-1933 (Box 27, Folder 384)
      Land utilization, village education movement, fellowships, traveling professorships.
    - China 0 - General, 1924-1933 (Box 27, Folder 385)
    - China 1 - University of Nanking, 1924-1933 (Box 27, Folder 386)
      Fellowships, plant improvement and breeding. Cornell. C. h. Meyers, H. H. Love.
    - China 1 - University of Nanking, 1924-1933 (Box 27, Folder 387)
    - China 1 - University of Nanking, 1924-1933 (Box 27, Folder 388)
    - China 1 - University of Nanking, 1924-1933 (Box 27, Folder 389)
    - China 1 - University of Nanking, 1924-1933 (Box 27, Folder 390)
      Fellowships, plant improvement and breeding. Cornell. C. H. Meyers, H. H. Love, R. G. Wiggans, John H. Reisner.
    - China 2 - Tsing Hua College, 1926 (Box 27, Folder 391)
    - China 3 - National Southeastern University, 1926 (Box 27, Folder 392)
    - China 4 - University of Nanking, 1926-1932 (Box 27, Folder 393)
    - Czechoslovakia 0 - General, 1924-1939 (Box 27, Folder 394)
    - Czechoslovakia 1 - Farm Demonstration Work, 1923-1926 (Box 27, Folder 395)
    - Denmark 0 - General, 1924-1930 (Box 27, Folder 396)
    - Denmark 1 - Farm Demonstration Work, 1923-1924 (Box 27, Folder 397)
      Boys and Girls Club; movies, equipment, fairs, agricultural education. Frants P. Lund, Soren Sorensen.
    - Denmark 1 - Farm Demonstration Work, 1925-1928 (Box 28, Folder 398)
    - Denmark 1 - Farm Demonstration Work, 1925-1928 (Box 28, Folder 399)
    - Denmark 1 - Farm Demonstration Work, 1925-1928 (Box 28, Folder 400)
    - Denmark 1 - Farm Demonstration Work - Reports (Box 28, Folder 401)
    - Denmark 2 - Frants P. Lund, 1923-1928 (Box 28, Folder 402)
    - Denmark 3 - Institute for Theoretical Physics, 1923-1927 (Box 28, Folder 403)
      Buildings, equipment, fellowships. Niels Bohr.
    - Denmark 4 - Krogh Institute of Physiology, 1923-1925 (Box 28, Folder 404)
      Buildings and equipment.
    - Denmark 5 - Scientific Publications, 1925 (Box 28, Folder 405)
    - Denmark 6 - University of Copenhagen, Laboratory of Physical Chemistry, 1925-1932 (Box 28, Folder 406)
      Buildings and equipment. J. N. Bronsted.
    - England 0 - General, 1923-1925 (Box 28, Folder 407)
      Universities, fellowships, libraries, conferences.
    - England 0 - General, 1923-1925 (Box 28, Folder 408)
    - England 0 - General, 1923-1925 (Box 28, Folder 409)
    - England 0 - General, 1926-1936 (Box 29, Folder 410)
    - England 0 - General, 1926-1936 (Box 29, Folder 411)
    - England 0 - General, 1926-1936 (Box 29, Folder 412)
    - England 0 - General, 1926-1936 (Box 29, Folder 413)
    - England 0 - General, 1926-1936 (Box 29, Folder 414)
    - England 0 - General, 1926-1936 (Box 29, Folder 415)
    - England 1 - Adult Education, 1923-1928 (Box 29, Folder 416)
      World Association for Adult Education. Albert Mansbridge.
    - England 1 - Adult Education, 1923-1928 (Box 29, Folder 417)
    - England 2 - Graham Balfour, 1923 (Box 29, Folder 418)
    - England 3 - University of London, 1923-1932 (Box 29, Folder 419)
    - England 3.1 - University of London, Botanical Research Institute in Regents Park, 1926-1928 (Box 29, Folder 420)
    - England 3.2 - University of London, School of Law, 1923-1927 (Box 29, Folder 421)
    - England 4 - Fellowship Conference Fund, 1923 (Box 30, Folder 422)
    - England 5 - Rothamsted Experimental Station, 1923-1929 (Box 30, Folder 423)
      Buildings.
    - England 5 - Rothamsted Experimental Station, 1923-1929 (Box 30, Folder 424)